free-pressrelease-distribution.com 2011-12-20

# Privacy Policy | FPRD

Please read this privacy policy carefully by using any of the services, you represent that you have read and understand the agreement, which includes this privacy policy and you agree to be bound by all its terms. We may change our privacy policy from time to time to address new issues and reflect changes on our sites, and as the need arises. All changes to this privacy policy will be posted here, please read this privacy policy every time you visit FPRD. If you have any questions or concerns about this privacy policy, please send us an e-mail at info@free-pressrelease-distribution.com.

**User Information:**  
User account information that you provide (such as your email address, address, phone number, passwords, etc.) is held in strict confidence and will not be sold or rented to the 3rd parties. The only time information is shared when a user of free- pressrelease-distribution.com submits their contact information during distribution of their press release.

**Information Collection and usage:**  
Our web servers automatically collect limited information about your computer’s connection to the Internet, including your IP address, when you visit our site. (Your IP address is a number that lets computers attached to the Internet know where to send you data — such as the web pages you view.) Your IP address does not identify you personally. We use this information to deliver our web pages to you upon request, to tailor our site to the interests of our users, and to measure traffic within our site.

**Sharing of Information:**  
We use third party advertisements on our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing Florida real estate ads to someone in Florida, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites). You can view their privacy policy by [clicking here](http://www.google.com/privacy.html).  
• Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site.  
• Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.  
We will comply with legal process served on us requiring the disclosure of user information and we may, at our discretion, disclose any user information requested by third parties as part of an investigation into the breach of our terms of service.  
We don’t share any voluntary or non-voluntary information gathered by us by means other than explained above.

**Cookies:**  
We may place a text file called a “cookie” in the browser files of your computer. The cookie itself does not contain Personal Information although it will enable us to relate your use of this site to information that you have specifically and knowingly provided. A cookie can’t read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. We use cookies to track user traffic patterns.

**Disclaimer:**  
FPRD disclaim any content found in news releases. Issuers of news releases are solely responsible for the accuracy of their content.
